opinions are free which is why we're
here it's news and talk that our
sponsors agree on
wct up next it's area 53 and Marvin
Trill broadcasting live from his trailer
in the desert a new planet found in
space is it really a planet or a decoy
put up to confuse us ghosts time travel
and the flushing toilet which way did
Newton's toilet spiral and finally our
women made from Sand we explore deeper
and get to the truth I'm Mar Trill this
is area 53 hello you're on the line yeah
hi I'm a truck driver and listen to your
show all the time I see a lot of
unexplained phenomena out there
especially in restrooms I agree with you
about the moon we never landed on the
moon it's such a good fake remember the
Russians our Arch Enemy still I might
add them and the Australians and some
species of dog they beat us into space
the only thing the Russians are shooting
into space are hot dogs and monkeys kind
of a noar fast food kind of vibe hey my
dad on could make a better space station
than them intriguing I'd like to meet
her on the conspiracy line caller you're
in area 53 you not use fluoride it's
evil it made me kill my doctor why would
we worry about a chemical that the
government puts into the water animals
can now be trained to fly including
several species of bird think about the
military applications hello caller hi my
name's Emanuel I'm really worried about
hackers sending a nuclear bomb after me
you know through the phones do you think
they can pinpoint my location look it's
good for the economy to live in constant
fear I mean the phone company they have
your name on the bill they know your
number how do you feel about that I knew
it hello Julie from Liberty City you're
on the line a cowboy ghost has been
haunting my house I want you to take off
your blouse stand at the window stand
there for hours each night lure him in
trapping Rogue Spirits is dangerous work
especially topless take lots of
photographs all right who's got a theory
for me next hey man love the show but
when are you guys going to start seeing
the bigger picture we're been lied to
man and guys like you don't help much
you know you're virtually one of them
soon you know what I'm talking about if
people could please just attempt to make
sense that's all I'm asking last night
as I was laying in my pod meditating and
it occurred to me why are you even
listening to me turn off all electrical
devices including your radio Hector in
San Garcia why are you still listening
because I was hoping could explain these
noises what noises God not you to now
think about the things we talked about
today think seriously think can it be
real can it be false we'll see you next
time in area 53 be careful out there
wherever you
are that was area 53 we're sorry
sometimes the law is not enough did you
file this opion in the mcferson case no
it wasn't urgent I filed an a440 a440 I
know I know so I went shopping for these
loafers has anyone got a stapler got a
lot of forms and there's a sight Breeze
in here because paperwork is dramatic
catch it Thursdays on weasel before it
catches you next up on wct the news we
try to make it interesting and not
depressing this this is Leanne for wct
news foreigners are coming who are they
and why should we care the FDA warns
shampoo is killing your unborn child
plus protests continue outside the zebra
bar candy company now for traffic and
Transit with Richard Burns that's right
lean I'm Richard Burns the aftermath of
the devastating earthquake continues
travel is still severely restricted
Statewide officials say there are still
no reported casualties which is truly
unfortunate as it makes for incredibly
boring news the federal government is
still refusing Aid to help rebuild
Bridges and everyone is blaming each
other the governor is threatening to
bomb Australia despite scientific proof
it wasn't their fault Richard Burns
wct police Say gang Trouble Is On The
Rise Again especially in Los Santos
sources believe it is linked to the
rising drugs trade While others blame
the fascist pigs also in gang news
Customs officials report a huge influx
of Russian mobsters and cheap weapons
since the fall of the wall the
governor's office said everything is
okay in Vinewood news rapper mad dog was
celebrating the launch of his new
clothing line Richard caught up with him
the thing about mad dog is I'm thinking
about becoming a superstar I mean you
know I've done everything I could do in
a rap game I want [ __ ] hands down nobody
can handle me you know lifetime champ no
[ __ ] can I say [ __ ] oh hey man it's cool
that's cool okay no [ __ ] I got clothes I
got labels coming out you know what I'm
saying I'm doing drinks I got shoes
tires rims thinking you know next stage
is being a full-on superstar you I get
to wear a tight suit and nail lot of
tail you dick you know what I do in real
life got to get me a drink though right
now cuz I'm thirsty you know what a
troubled man sounds like he should lay
off the sauce also today a Tourette's
theater group banned from the park
unless they take up mine and finally in
foreign news a suspected us agent was
caught in Panama selling Weaponry to
right-wing gorillas causing a major
incident but plan mostly to gloss over
the implications and hope you enjoy some
sporting activity tonight the state
department is advising against foreign
travel this was lean forj wct news let's
be careful out there up next on wct it's
the man coach's hate it's Derek ther in
the tight end zone brought to you by ays
PumpUp shoes because women love a winner
and winners wear shoes should we uh
start with the national
anthem yeah screw it yeah I got I got
too drunk last night just uh play the
opening
music welcome back to the tight zone now
it's time for something really important
fat men talking about games they don't
really understand played by people they
don't know I'm your host dere
zory what a crazy year it's been let's
recap drug scandals involving preschool
soccer
moms woo and the National Finals rich
and popular people are fighting it out
pay attention the country is in
morning and most importantly Sports
where we talked to a fitness expert
about the crucial role of endorsed
clothing and who could forget we visit
the greatest
moments here he comes he's in the
shadows there he is is he going to make
it yes he did ladies and gentlemen what
you have just witnessed is the biggest
moment in world history who cares about
a decaration of Independence or
discovery of penicillin you have just
seen one man score a point when the rest
of the world discovers TV they'll be
able to see this wow isn't that amazing
he did what he was paid to do we love
sports more than you love it or loath it
let's talk about it stay in the tight
end
zone let's go to the
phones yeah the Wolves hey Derek my name
is Jason and I'm a wolves fan first time
caller I don't vote I can't be bothered
but I will kick your ass if you
disrespect my sports team okay the
Wolves that's a team playing sports as
if they cared yeah the Wolves I don't
care who's sleeping with who on the team
yeah I'm with you buddy okay hey let's
take another call who's on the phone
hello caller you're on with a tight end
of radio hey I'm a big Olympics fan
always have been since day one been to
everyone me too I love the games
especially the
lose I'm married so uh slide down an icy
tunnel of Doom at high speed makes sense
yeah I know about frigid action myself I
mean they got to be kidding me since
when has running been an Olympic sport
running ain't a sport don't make me puke
anyone can run my ex-wife made me an
athlete I ran my ass off when the Red
Baron flew into town I tell you when I
was a kid there were only three sports
that mattered football baseball and
killing Communists and uh I had a great
childhood really great even if my uncle
did come into my room that late at night
drunk and oh that was nuts any anyway
look who's on the line we got a
caledonians fan on the line tough times
huh hey uh your whole life revolving
around rich men playing poorly man I
totally identify with shallow Heroes who
I don't know personally God I love a
dude with a big pituitary gland I love
the Callie man but you know this year
I'm telling you they're going to need to
score some points and get some yardage
and win the game yeah if they don't win
men will be beating their wives with
good reason hey they got to start
playing to win trying to score some on
the other team I wish I had a wife so
she could beat me here's what I say man
if you want to be number one you got to
go for first place I know I know hey I
mean uh you know it's great stay in the
obvious but once you get paid for it
things get really complicated man I was
at their training camp this spring and
the mood in the locker room dude got
guys were getting changed man I mean
they were really getting prepared shoes
were going on feet shirts were going on
the shirt part of their body serious
faces on them and you could tell that
they were going to play this game bottom
line is if they don't score more points
than the other team they can't win yeah
man God you have some spooky insights
into sports dude I love your show man I
I love
you yeah look great talking to you
excuse me hey that's really perceptive
stuff you know we've been petitioning
stadiums to install a urinal trough in
front of each row of seats now it's so
inconvenient having to leave your seat
make everyone stand up get up get up you
know to to let you buy then go stand in
line for the bathroom I mean half the
time we can barely walk anyway all right
so we'll be handing out petitions that
say support the team don't leave the
game pee at your seat go the phones I'm
a big fight fan love a bit of a punch up
since my wife and children got taken
into a shelter my friend said Chuck you
obviously love hitting things so I've
gotten into boxing how about that fight
between Gonzalez and Jackson well
there's one thing about boxing I always
remember you know one man wins the other
goes home a loser because in boxing
unlike most Sports Gravity Works
downwards you got to be [ __ ] me hey
Derek ther don't [ __ ] on no one but uh I
do like to piss on my seat and uh at my
seat too not really on it so stay out of
the way tell me the five game that ain't
rigged is it of course not hey how could
anything professional be fake hey
there's too much money at stake for one
thing I mean these guys got too much to
lose I mean why is a guy going to take a
dive for a few extra million when he
could earn that over a number of years
getting his brain turned to pulp be
serious for a minute the clock is
counting down again it's time for Derek
to head to the locker room and celebrate
in the shower with we'll see you next
time bring a cooler full of beers and
get ready to Riot this has been the
tight end
zone and this is wct proving that radio
is better than TV that's the show men
with large guts love deal with your
ignorance in one minute flat complex
issues in 60 seconds
wct coming up next the most mind-numbing
thing since the labotomy entertaining
America this week on entertaining
America Richard Goblin one man's
triumphant return to [ __ ] the Sherman
octuplets a venturous man says he's
slept with them all plus noise speed
danger cursing and patriotism finally
come together this weekend at the All
America drunk driving cup hi from
Vinewood you're on entertaining America
with me Billy Dexter bringing you
everything that is important in culture
and entertainment if there is a
difference between the from the heart of
entertainment in America Vinewood San
Andreas you with me the decks wanted to
call the show stack the de but not yet
Klum anyway Great Big Show for you this
week controversy they'll be giving me a
pullitzer anyway today we've got some
great guests first up we speak to
troubled Action Hero Jack Howitzer then
we have a live phone leak up with a very
special guest modern day Lazarus a man
back from the grave now making it as an
extra in major Motion Pictures then I
will explain the secrets of the universe
to everyone but first up stack the decks
in which I Billy Dexter meet the
entertainers in the news
klam Jack Howitzer once the biggest star
in America but the last three years have
been unkind people describe him as a
dinosaur an action hero Relic from the
80s a musclebound neanderthal and my
favorite the most stupid gorilla in the
Jungle Jack welcome to the show KL good
to be here deck's pleasure yeah so
you're movies Exploder and Annihilator
got America through some tough times and
I was also a huge fan of of 0 seconds to
death time thank thank you but many say
your new film has gone too far no this
is a romantic comedy with drama it's got
action it's got a heart that's what's
most important I think okay well let's
take a listen to the trailer all right
let's roll
that he was a man at war with himself
fighting a war that someone else lost
it's over Tim the war's over it's never
over
you've seen him wipe out millions of
cambodians in Exploder now Jack Howitzer
is Tim in his most challenging role yet
we're here Tim a preschool for slow
children you're the new teacher Tim
special needs cop it's the story of a
psychotic xmarine showing tough love to
special ed kids one of you tdds has been
running Peruvian flake through the
special ed school and I'm going to find
it no juice and cookies M suck him but
soon he becomes one of them what is this
that's teacher's gun you want to see
it oh you got and shot yourself way to
go he was finally beginning to live a
normal life then all hell breaks loose
Tim you're so stupid you count with your
fingers you want to party with me bring
it on damn what are you doing I fought
for my country welcome to the land of
Freedom
[ __ ] special needs come he had a lot
to learn this film cannot be rated wow
that's terrible no wonder our studios
are surrounded by protest how could
anybody find that offensive no no Jack
it's appalling your insensitive
portrayal of disabled people makes me
physically sick and the idea of you
calling someone slow wited is frankly
laugh hold on hold on drugs are a
problem throughout all of society and I
fight them by any means necessary but
you use drugs no no no I'd rather die
than use drugs I use steroids and some
recreational blow but I got the funds
for it you know I got the money yeah
don't you think you're just a little out
of touch whoa whoa whoa whoa yeah I'm
rich and I work in Vinewood okay I'm not
out of touch action weightlifting and
killing foreigners that never goes out
of style decks my last film okay loin
cloth about a wrestler who's dropped
into Thailand and I saved the World by
teabagging the bad guys that's a
spiritual picture that's love teabagging
that stuff ain't out of style yeah
things are more sensitive now I was
affected all right when hoi got hurt an
Exploder I mean I I thought it was time
to do something a film that made a
difference he but hoochi was a character
Exploder was a movie right right and I
was there and I should have killed them
all don't push me Dex I'll give you a
war you won't believe that look in your
eye right here right now okay oh Jack
Jack all I'm saying is you launching
missiles from a special wheelchair and
killing innocent civilians is somewhat
insensitive there's never any innocent
civilians in life if the Reds roll down
the street right now what are you going
to do the Red's lost man it's it's over
you can come home I'll shoot those
bastards with this the family killer
Jack Jack put that away please what this
it's a submachine gun come on it's not
serious oh but you're Billy Dexter who
put you up to this Gorbachev no no you
should come down I heard what you said
about me you think St shank my genital
no no put the gun down please I'm I'm
sure you have huge ones please stop come
on they haven't shrunk touch them feel
them come on stiff them do something
touch them touch them or die they're
still big oh God they're huge Jack yeah
Mom M don't grab him like that oh boy I
was kidding what are you a boyfriend of
mine or something hey hey hey you have
me scared there for a minute I I I I
crapped myself take it easy it's not
even loaded
oh oh Dex oh [ __ ] oh well I guess it was
oh okay Billy don't get around get up
boy get up come on damn it his brain is
leaking help oh there's only one thing
to do I got to defend Freedom no time to
cry only time to die welcome to the land
of Freedom
[ __ ] that was entertaining America
showing you why America is so respected
culturally across the world prepare to
be scared the news is
next this is Leanne for wct news pop
sensation Crow threatens to stop singing
America celebrates and movies are they
true plus children was Freud right do
they want us all dead now a wctr
exclusive with Richard Burns that's
right Leanne I'm Richard Burns crime in
Los Santos has skyrocketed with
officials saying carjacking murder
robbery and gang activity is all on the
rise police described it as and I'm
quoting here nothing to worry about I
met up with a real life carjacker
earlier who showed me the ropes I call
it the three G you just grab get in and
go oh my God you're in so much trouble
you shut up [ __ ] yeah you be quiet
[ __ ] this is a news story oh cool this
is great this is quality journalism uh
back to you Leanne hey let's get blunted
and grab some clucking Bell I have got
Mad Munchies sounds good to me fire it
up dude you got any papers youth
counselors in Los Santos are heading to
the streets and meeting one-on-one with
members of the community one citizen
told wctr the real problem with drugs
they always saying it's too many drugs
in the hood homie that's [ __ ] plain
[ __ ] I mean way I see it is it ain't
enough drugs in the hood ain't nothing
like enough and that's the real problem
for people police still have no leads in
the tragic murder of of Officer Ralph
pendlebury whose body was found recently
pendlebury worked for internal affairs
it was believed he was close to
uncovering a huge corruption ring within
the LSPD a police spokesman denied the
story a San Fiero man is suing the
renaissance fair for selling him replica
Weaponry which he blames for a string of
murders Richard caught up with him I
purchased a working catapult at the
renaissance fair and after a fight with
my insurance salesman over my DWI I
began lobbing Balls of Fire at his house
and burnt down an entire neighborhood
it's inexcusable the manufacturers will
pay give me some money come on give me
some money it's their fault what kind of
a person sells a catapult without
putting a very clear warning on the side
I don't want to work very hard so I've
hired a lawyer I'm going to be rich
seems fair enough to me I'm Leanne for
that was the news be safe out
[Music]
there hello uh Mom it's me Jimmy how
great to hear from you how are you not
good Mom I killed a man drunk driving I
need bail money bad oh can you uh
remortgage the house every day is
Mother's Day San Andre's telephone for
those difficult conversations have you
heard the number one gardening show in
San Andreas if not here's what you're
missing well why don't you just go buy
your vegetables at the grocery store
then you sick offence God I just don't
understand people you go to hell well
screw you too my M see if you're ever on
the show again next caller hello yeah
what's that plant that blooms every 12
years is OT high and smells like hell I
want to plant one on my ex-wife's lawn
it's called amorphofalis
titanium God I love to say that
amorphofalis
titanium and the sound of it gives me a
redwood in my khakis if I come back as a
superhero I want to be called that it's
a morph ofis titanium the rare Botanical
Wonder see his 8ot cruson as he
pollinates on everyone but why does it
sting so bad it's about marking your
territory my man you don't Mark your
territory do you you should try it pee
on the front door of your office just
see if anybody thinks of coming near you
okay I I'll I would try that thank you
so much for the advice Maurice oh I'm
here to help sailor gardening with
Maurice only on
wct in darkness you only have your
nocturnal instincts to rely on Ultimate
in the dark the electric stimulating new
game that's sweeping San Fiero it's a
non- contct contact sport where you
throw a flying disc in the dark I got it
get him nail his ass it's a new
competitive sport for the uncompetitive
an aggressive action-packed game for
those who love nature and living on the
edge it's harder than football it's
faster than rugby it's about throwing a
plastic disc and catching it pitch then
catch run to the goal and score ultimate
disc in the dark just like a real sport
only we made it up and it has is a great
social side oh my God what team are you
on I'm on the other team me too H take
that silly but if you catch it you got
to know what to do with it some will
struggle some will submit everyone is
laughing but it's your quest to come out
on top this is a great excuse for some
serious fun and a way to meet people
like you and never see them again League
games begin at Sunset every night in San
Fiero Civic Park or start your own game
and because it's night it's not too
embarrassing to play a strip version
come and play ultimate disc in the dark
talk is cheap especially on this station
featuring more Rich angry people
complaining
wct do you find your daughter's friends
attractive but know they look at you as
just a dad does the typing pool at work
think of you more as a teddy bear than a
tiger do you whack off in your minivan
while listening to teen pop you know
you'll be dead soon you've missed out on
so much it's not too late to make a
change at the midlife crisis center we
know you've made a success of yourself
why are you sharing it with others why
not enjoy it while you have a chance
what's holding you back cowardice we'll
get you to the other side of your
despair we specialize in real estate
divorce attorneys mistress placement
plastic surgery hair coloring and
replacement male fur coats and much more
with a designer clothing store and
sports car dealership on site the
midlife crisis center will help you
discover Life while you still still can
come with your wife leave with a sports
car while you've made a success of
yourself her chest has gone South how
can you have that trollop on your arm
for a second longer the answer is you
can't ignore your children take yourself
seriously visit the midlife crisis
center today it's a favorite show with
serial killers and stalkers Lonely
Hearts is
next alter the sultry anonymity of night
and some of the day you're on lonely
hearts on wct West Coast talk radio or
as I like to call it we can't talk right
I love you all I'm your host Christy
McIntyre let's go to the phones hi
Christy my wives and I love your show
it's really helped a thanks do you want
to tell us about it uh
no okay Jenny on the line from Santa
Maria hi Jenny how's your heart broken
like my arm and two of my ribs what
happened I married my childhood
sweetheart but it all went wrong he's
become a drunk and he has a substance
problem too and now he beats me every
day stay with him honey after all you're
only lonely when you're alone but he
keeps threatening to kill me Jenny do
you know the meaning of the phrase home
wrecker no what about selfish [ __ ] I
want to bring people together not break
them apart who's on the phones it's a
big lonely State out there K Mary I'm
watching you right now in the shower
notice how many lonely hearts are
lunatics you wonder why or perhaps not
Brian from Las Venturas hey dude my
name's Brian I'm calling from Las
Venturas I want to talk about my heart
why do man just repeat back what you say
and never listen are you brain dead
Brian oh actually it's ironic that you
say that was cuz my wife's been brain
dead for years now oh so sorry I seemed
all insensitive for a second there
possibly ruining my career would it help
if I slept with you probably not do it
though she wouldn't even notice I mean I
get away with it all the time now even
after I did it with her sister actually
our relationship is better than ever the
passion is amazing it's like I'm a new
person each time if she was back to the
way she was before the accident wow I'd
put her in a coma myself I mean it's
fantastic that's very informative you
know last night I wondered what it would
be like to be brain dead then I watched
my five uncles God I'd love to live in
that house remember a heart can men but
a divorce lasts forever unless he makes
you a widow hello yeah hello lonely HS
uh I was just calling up there cuz I was
listening and I figured out you know
that I can help out some of y'all
clients you know this is none other than
Jizzy the proprietor of the pleasure
domes Club if anybody is out there
lonely first of all with all the people
on this planet walking around it's no
reason for anybody to be lonely you
understand that's why I'm in the
business of keeping people with company
you know what I'm saying people who got
low self-esteem and they need to pick me
up they need to come down to the
pleasure Dome hang out with me just busy
and My Girls you know what I'm saying
they going to keep your company have you
feeling good and this goes for everybody
I don't care who you are how old you are
so come on down and hang out with me if
you're lonely and I'm going tell you
something you won't be lonely from the
moment you walk in the door cuz
somebody's going to grab your hand and
it's going to be all about to get down
from that good grief that's not the way
Ling Hearts works at all is anyone here
suffering I want pain misery desolation
all the important things hi this is
Tamara I'm a stalker Ah that's really
beautiful tell everyone about it my man
well I call him that even though he's
broken off all contact and is married to
someone else I killed a gazelle and sent
its heart to him in an envelope he liked
it so much he told the police and even
the newspapers then I burnt down his
place of business and now I have a
special surprise for him you have a
great week isn't that really beautiful
that's all we have time for if your
heart is lonely listen to other losers
and you won't be lonely anymore you'll
want to spend the rest of your life in
isolation away from people which is
progress after all until next time I
hope you enjoyed Lonely Hearts it's
always fun to laugh at other people's
misery isn't it deal with your ignorance
in one minute flat complex issues in 60
seconds
wct let's be honest about things for a
second really honest you came out to the
West Coast to get away from something
everyone does let's face it the Midwest
is full of retards that's why we've got
the fastest growing population a massive
economy and absolutely no history or
culture you used to be a dork but you
moved here and suddenly you're cool San
Andreas is a land where you can be who
you want to be change your name come out
lie about your age form your own
religion call yourself an actor at
weight tables it just doesn't matter out
here everybody's at it until the awful
moment old friends or family come to
visit Janice understands maybe it's time
to change your identity don't let bad
memories blow your cover we'll teach you
all the things you need to alienate your
family quick they'll never think of
visiting you again select from a list of
weird religions that involve burning
things singing children's songs
backwards and loads of Television
worship we'll select a member of another
race or life form for you to claim as
your soulmate and your dietary habits
will go Pacific too people come to San
Andreas to escape their past we'll help
you lose contact with friends and family
fast Janice it's time to invent the new
you the news and all the other things
that really matter to you like
sensationalist
[ __ ] sexual realignment used to
require expensive of surgery months of
hormone treatments years of therapy and
you still ended up looking like a drag
queen now you can let the woman Inside
come out in the privacy and comfort of
your own home and it's as fast as this
slice see now I'm a woman thanks to
rapidy this do-it-yourself sexual
realignment kit includes everything you
need to go from Brad to Brenda in a gif
it's just snip chop stuff and swallow
and Away you go do it in the bathroom
and surprise your family with a new you
comes with with an instructional video
Rusty knife and tourniquet two aspirins
and 47 lb of estrogen it's all you need
when it's time for a change you want it
fast rapidit the do-it-yourself sexual
realignment kit be exactly who you want
to
be if you love to hear liberals wine and
conservatives lecture then stay tuned
for I say you say the future of America
threatened again this time we mean it
I'm Dr Phillips and I'm also Dr Phillips
today on the show decave paintings in
museum make us violent the anti- beef
movement both Hitler and musolini were
vegetarians and we take on the highly
charged debate about test two babies and
actually talk to one I have flashbacks
and go to hysterics and science class do
you know what it's like growing up in a
beaker that's all today on I say
us we share last names but that's about
it I'm pton that's my wife Mary and this
is I say you say where left is right and
right is wrong or East Meets West and
the West always wins that wall came down
darling yes unfortunately it did I I
don't know if you saw today's news so
who is in the right in this great
dialectical disaster is it as I think a
case of share and share alike love your
fellow man and all wear matching
jumpsuits while working on a collective
hydroponic Farm growing potatoes or kill
or be killed crush the weak and starve
the poor as my wonderful wife thinks you
decide or let us decide for you give us
a call and let my wife a professor in
Social Darwin ISM or me a lecturer in
pointless anthropology work things out
that's the problem with liberals they
don't know when to shut up and enjoy
Freedom let's go to the phones uh yeah
Hi here's the deal I'm really funny but
nobody wants to hire somebody funny I I
mean how is that fair I I mean I'm white
middle class very aidite um you know
whatever that means but people just
respond badly to me I I don't understand
it are you related to my
husband uh I don't think so I hope not
have you got a question about politics
yeah sure I know a lot about politics
hey can I do your job you know I used to
be on the radio back in the day even my
husband can't do his job you strange
pathetic little sap let's have a real
caller please hi my name is Michelle I'm
a first time caller to the show I wanted
to know what you guys thought about the
proposition to ban smoking well this is
a simple issue smoking democracy at work
again in our state seems like a good
thing when you first look at it but
democracy only works when you agree with
it then it's best to favor a
totalitarian state I'm not sure about
this one I think smoking is an invasion
of my body and I've always wanted to
shoot people I'm right behind the
proposition me too thanks Michelle I
also wanted to say hi to my stepbrother
Phil who's been undergoing a hair
transplant today hey Phil if you're
listening I hope it's six this time I
won't tell anyone you've got plugs honey
I'm really proud of you that's great
honey but if you want shout outs call
the rap station that's offensive and I'm
really offended by what you're saying
I'm a smoker this used to be a free
country when good point darly got you're
good yes good point but remember our
founding fathers grew tobacco it relaxed
them between stressful stints of
genocide and witch burning and you're so
against raising taxes smokers pay more
taxes than anyone my grandfather smoked
his whole life and he lived until he was
32 so what I'm saying is why can't we
encourage more smoking and use the money
to pay for better healthare and some
cultural programs bringing expressive
dance and Sun worship back to the inner
cities worrying about the inner city has
ruined your academic career and this
woly thinking is going to ruin your
chances of getting anywhere with me
tonight promise the thing is smoking is
good because it lets people make a lot
of money but so is selectively culling
the population so what I'm proposing is
a change in the proposition let people
smoke but make cigarettes much cheaper
and force everyone to smoke that way we
weed out the week make a lot of money
and tax and keep our National Heritage
intact line two you're on I say you say
ha I listen every time to your show it
really made me think about the world the
whole new way I moved out of the city
cuz it sucks now I live in a compound
surrounded by barb wire and shoot and
kill anyone I don't recognize all my
land just want to say thank you that's
some quality broadcasting yeah thanks
that makes me feel a lot better about
myself have you got a question yeah I
got corpses from 15 illegal immigrants
in my yard I killed them all myself with
my bare hands can I get a tax break for
all this unpaid work good good question
I would certainly hope so ask your
accountant if you can register them as
dependents then hide most of your net
worth offshore at a complex money
laundering system designed to support
the drugs trade then you can pay
virtually no taxes and complain about
how awful you think the whole country is
knowing you're doing as little as
possible to help cool thanks that's good
advice I'm appalled at you Mary Phillips
why because that man has a garden full
of corpses and you're talking about
money laundering yes it's a great
opportunity for some profit Centric
thinking you missed a wonderful
opportunity to talk about Recycling and
organ donation oh God give me strength I
married a fool I married a fo you know
when we first met Payton I thought you
were So Glamorous with your long hair
and big Ideas you were studying for a
PhD in cultural ceramic history or cross
cultural underwear or something and I
was very young very foolish now I see
you for what you are and what's that
exactly an intellectual cess pit a
middle class disaster a guilt trip
wrapped in neurosis and completely
unable to function in this Society no
wonder I've begun to sleep around and on
that note we have to go visit our
marriage therapist who was a conniving
[ __ ] and won't write me any more
prescriptions for painkillers remember
when the left wing and the right wing
come together the country can really get
going straight off a cliff we'll see you
next
time boy I can't imagine what those guys
are like in the bedroom but I'm sure
it's a bit like the Bay of Pigs that was
I say you say at home at work or in
rehab Listen to
wct Next Up we've got the news this time
some of it's true who are we
kidding I'm Leanne for wct news here's
everything that matters in simple terms
so you can understand a dire warning
from America's gun manufacturers learn
yourself or die and the Louisiana
Purchase B for women plus wallpaper
something big is happening in home
furnishings don't be left behind our top
story Alan Crawford manager of the
rapper Mad Dog murdered Mad Dog recently
launched a clothing label and compared
himself favorably to Jesus and Gandhi
while sniffing a lot the brutal murder
remains unsolved police suspect Foul
Play Richard Burns is at the scene uh no
actually Leanne that story wasn't very
interesting so I rode with San Fiero
police detective Turk Martin who is
assigned a cur tail illegal street
racing activities in the countryside
surrounding Los Santos and San Fiero you
know what's really cool you get to taste
these slime balls really fast and if you
hit someone W it's never your fault oh
this is so cool you get to eat while you
work let me see that hey stop now
[ __ ] or we'll shoot out your tires
put that down ah dude don't be a dick
let me shoot out his tires I'm doing
like 110 mph right now
okay in foreign news a heavily
discredited former dictator in Latin
America is claiming a US government
agency sold him weapons in exchange for
drugs that are now being sold on the
streets of our cities government
officials strongly deny the claim why
would we do something so crazy we don't
need drugs we have good hookups already
besides which do you know how much
cocaine is needed to buy a helicopter
it's more than I can snort lean for wct
news stay worried out there
come live the
mystery
Str cool off in our water sports park
I'll show your kids a great time it's
something they'll never forget and talk
about for years to come especially at
therapy sessions it's the place for
magic and
Adventure leaving me free to shop and
get Lio who's ready for the incredible
dribbles Voyage Sherry can we come too
this is a Journey you must undertake
alone can be dark and scary she'll shrip
with Del
light what's that home a wall for you a
and see you'll be amazed [ __ ] the
suit glory hole theme park open every
day till 3:00 a.m. today we marched on
from Fort struther after Sunrise to a
Creek Village where our troops fought
the Savages and shot them like dogs
honey it's time for bed hang on a second
I'm killing a squa take that you Pagan
[ __ ] no no him and his commemorative
Miniatures my husband was getting so
boarded workking and he didn't have an
interest to spend money on but he's
always loved history then I heard about
grown men who like to play with Toy
Soldiers war is so interesting with
commemorative Miniatures I began by
Faithfully rebuilding The Charge of the
Light Brigade and after that the Trail
of Tears I've built accurate Recreations
of 15 significant battles as well as
training camps prisoner War camps and
forced labor death camps now I spend all
my time painting toy soldiers and
attending conventions commemorative
Miniatures they're instantly collectible
and a great value for just 37 monthly
payments of$ 1999 you get a starter pack
allowing you to recreate the Battle of
your choice show your inability to deal
with present-- day Problems by
recreating scenes of Mass Slaughter from
the past reenacting battles is great for
your marriage too one night my husband's
General Custer the next Napoleon on
Saturdays I'm a Cambodian vill
and he's a GI that has his way with me
then I kill her commemorative Miniatures
they're not toys they're very valuable
collectible 2-in P model armies this is
a hobby you can't afford to miss out on
if you're into exploring exotic places
and forbidden fruit stay tuned it's the
wild traveler next support for the wild
traveler is brought to you by the
ultimate disc in the- dark Association
of America who encourages you to get out
and play
hard hello I'm James pistan World
traveler and this is the wild traveler
we're discussing the world and all of
its many Pleasures let me put it like
this why have a hot dog from an uncaring
Vendor by the bathroom when you can
attend a beer guzzling marathon in
Germany with enormous men and taste a
wonderful Germans Bo the world is full
of
inedible things and you can discover
them for yourself come along I'll take
you there
it was Dusk and the sun bled red over
the city in Thailand as Chen brought me
a sparkling water a delicate handsome
lovely young boy the world of
possibilities but war is folly and we
can only unite by visiting these epochs
of culture where a man can be himself
smoke cigarettes dress in Gladiator
clothing if he likes we mustn't Force
our way and culture upon other peoples
rather breathe it in become part of it
maybe Hemingway was right about love
maybe fraud was we're all fighting
inside to let a wild creature mate in
the rain I travel therefore I am this is
a show that Embraces culture from around
the world let's take our first caller
hello yeah I totally agree with you
about Australia and you're right the
Moon is [ __ ] also I was thinking of
visiting Columbia do you have any
recommendations oh is fantastic forms of
recreation to be had in Colombia it's a
blizzard of excitement and cheap the
rails are great and long Bolivia is not
bad either or Peru you'll be surprised
to find out how the party never stops
how's the food well a lighter is the
most you need to cook up food but
there's scarcely time to eat my boy
you'll meet Fascinating People feel so
comfortable you'll rip your clothes off
and
how for days next caller yeah hi my my
name is Geraldine calling from CA City
this is such a great country why would
you go anywhere else it's unpatriotic to
travel I mean I got War famine
depression and pollution right here on
my doorstep and parents don't let kids
you're a rail after college they'll come
back with ludicrous misconceptions about
Healthcare charity and civilization
Europe is not the real world this is
well I love to slum about in a dirty
youth hostel with communal showers as
much as the next man sometimes more but
I have to agree Europe is overrated
Eastern Europe was good for a few years
after the wall came down but even there
the police are too strict you just can't
let your hair down there are far more
unexplored Pleasures to be had in the
Far East next caller you're on the wild
traveler hey I've been listening to you
go on and on about traveling do you know
how expensive it is to fly to Asia
Russia saw the light they're all coming
here to set up crime families and run
numbers South America everyone went a
extinct there they have less culture
there than the content of my toilet bowl
rainforest Shain forest in Mexico if I
wanted to be that close to my ancient
ancestors I'd be banging my
mother-in-law instead of my wife's best
friend look we can fight like beasts or
agree to disagree I'm sure the summit of
your aspirations in life is a
cheerleader with fake guns but some of
us think a little more exotically than
this next caller vamus buenos Di and
noes if you don't smile I won't deep
harder sorry got lost for a second speak
hey I love this show I'm a huge fan I
visit all the places you've recommended
and in a lot of them they're still
talking about you I even saw posters of
you in the Customs booth at the airport
in the Philippines you rock and no doubt
I Lov Manila had a great time but that
show you did last week what was the name
of that spiritual center in Bangkok the
wild Dragon happy ending very spiritual
you will find inner peace awesome I
can't wait thanks man yes we all love to
travel get away from it all get away
from the people with computers in their
databases the police harassing you for
doing nothing I just hate showing up to
someplace to enjoy myself and people are
being forced from their homes by war or
famine or whatever life is great stop
ruining it next caller hey the FBI wants
to talk to me about a perfectly innocent
collection of vacation photographs
overseas that I had no idea were being
taken I mean any ignorant fool can
misinterpret I I was teaching them how
to swim I have a lot of experience with
this I want you to stop for a moment and
let me read from my travel Journal I
think everyone should keep a journal
paste pictures notes sometimes people
object to you taking their picture but a
few pennies of their local currency and
they will fa over you some people think
this is patronizing but I think it is
fair enough they need the money and I
need the company besides which it is the
oldest profession
what oh time for me to head south again
I'm James piston and this has been the
wild
traveler this is wct committed to
bringing you shows like the wild
traveler the show that takes you around
the world and abandons you at the
airport if you crave News
wct West Coast talk radio next up it's
Sensational as propaganda I mean the
news
I'm Leanne for wct news here's what you
should think matters breaking news
strange lights spotted over the desert
here's an eyewitness report I seen some
strange lights over the
desert yep sure did currently we have no
more information in other news residents
are upset at taxes funding the Los
Santos Museum of Natural History this
fascination with the past is ridiculous
I mean I've been to Pangia it was
disgusting in our ancestors were idiots
my grandmother can barely talk she's so
stupid also organ theft how to know if
you're going to wake up in a bathtub of
ice more gang violence we go to the
streets of Los Santos with Richard Burns
that's right Leanne I'm Richard Burns
and I am in a terrible part of town a
town Under Siege by hoodlums gang and
drug wars are plaguing the city hey you
went this part or what yeah just put it
in the van a huge sudden upsurge in
cocaine sales have been reported the
street Wars between gangs of Ballas and
Grove Street hoodlums came to a head
recently when several senior Grove
Street gang members were killed while
others were incarcerated the police
describe that as and I'm quoting
excellent news back to you Leanne hey
has this been cut hell no it's good [ __ ]
Bridges linking Red County and Flint
County finally reopened recently after
long delays following the earthquake the
governor congratulated himself
extensively in entertainment news first
it was the budgies then it was love fist
now the British Invasion starts up again
this time from the Scottish Village of
madchester new band The gning Chimps are
tipped for stardom we caught up with the
lead singer Macker when he landed in Los
Santos airport the ging chimps are
coming to America man we're going to
take over M my words and wipe my [ __ ]
ass lock up your daughters and get the
drugs in Manchester's in the area lean
for wct news keep it locked on it's
getting worse out
there the news and all the other things
that really matter to you like
sensationalist
[ __ ] coming up next it's time for
the man who can grow anything big and
strong it's gardening with Maurice
broadcasting live from his
garden howdy Doodles this is gardening
with Maurice and I am Maurice ever since
man was kicked out of the garden he's
been striving to get back in I believe
all of life's answers can be found in
something as simple as a flower it's
stamman it's pistol it's pollin just
like me and you we're going to the
phones hello you're on gardening with
Maurice I am Maurice go ahead caller uh
yes thanks for having me on I'm a big
fan uh I have a question my melons
aren't big enough I thought they were
going to keep growing but they just
stopped my next door neighbor has huge
melons and everyone just spawns over
them oh they taste so sweet oh look how
firm they are what do I do oo I would
love to see your melons look gardening
is a spiritual light Journey where you
become one with nature however sometimes
nature needs some chemicals to you know
kind of kick things into action there's
a fantastic fertilizer I use called
piteri it needs to be injected with a
needle so be very very careful and
inject that right into your melons and
they will grow enormous thanks so much
Maurice you're the best yes I know I
know that I've been at one with nature
for so long now I can't remember what
it's like to sleep inside next caller
God I was on hold forever uh I've heard
that facials are great really make you
look younger oh yes listen honey I
should know when you look like a train
wreck you need a little makeup or some
such you sound like a lonely spinster
with two [ __ ] cats it's the menopause
Maurice I'm having hot flashes okay
taking a pause from men huh you know I
should try that for your face try
Nature's cosmetic camouflage Cleopatra
took milk baths with cereal each morning
try Tomatoes too the acid is great it
makes your face just peel right off hey
thanks Maurice that's me fertilizing
Minds enough of you voyers out there and
your vicarious gardening I want you to
join in on the fun when you stick your
hands in the mystery of Nature and you
pull out a worm or a tuber God I love
tubers so plump and juicy hello Mike
from prickle Pine in Los venturus hey
Maurice first time caller my name is
Mike I work on my lawn and garden all
weekend long cuz I got this raging edus
complex and I like drinking beer and
riding around on the lawnmower too
because you know the vibrations are kind
of cool but what really killing me is I
can't seem to get these weeds out of the
driveway I tried Napal I tried gasoline
of course okay stop stop stop stop stop
st listen I want you to listen to me are
you listening to me Mark it's Mike okay
good that was a test okay I know what
your name is I know it's Mark now listen
up listen closely I want you to pave
over your entire yard okay I want you to
just pave it over with cement or
asphalt or whatever listen I have the
Maurice Mansion completely covered in
AstroTurf inside and outside which by
the way is particularly handy when some
big football players come over and we
have a little midnight match of ultimate
disc in the yard now when your lawn is
beautiful and green all year long you
can focus on the important matters if
you get my drift you see gardening with
Maurice is sponsored by the happy farmer
Yahoo if you're afraid someone will
steal your Tomatoes why not grow
tomatoes in your closet indoors like me
the happy farmer Hydroponics and more
next story to blos I'm Maurice until
next time dig a hole and plant
yourself that was the show that
generates more phone calls than any
other on wct gardening with Maurice the
news and all the other things that
really matter to you like people dying
lady on fire bodies everywhere and
explosions is hanging from the trees
this accident is really cool wct
need to meet someone very special Lonely
Hearts is next welcome to Lonely Hearts
the place where we make dreams come true
where we bring people together and we
remind you about what really matters in
matters of the heart great abs and a fat
wallet hi lonely hearts on the phone
speak hello my name is zero I'm a
first-time caller and uh uh to the show
I've used the telephone before but I am
having real trouble with women I I don't
know
any yes I don't know any well we all go
through lean spells you know after a
drought you'll sell for anything that
drops out of the sky especially illegal
immigrants stowed away in the landing
gear so exotic no no no I I do I I
masturbate quite often if that's what
you're implying I'm I'm just saying uh
this is quite a lean spell lady well
that's too bad still after winter comes
spring and after the rain the trees
blossom and drop leaves and [ __ ] all
over my yard well this is quite to
Winter do you understand what I'm saying
try try a nuclear winter I've never even
been near a woman close enough to gra I
don't know what to say well that's odd
considering you give advice I don't
think I can help look I'm just being
honest here I wouldn't even subject you
to a hooker please lady I don't want to
be celibate there's a lot of people out
there with a vow of celibacy and look at
all the joy they bring to the world I'd
love to help but it sounds serious and I
like to keep things strictly trivial
who's on the phone how's your heart I
saw documentary about this serial killer
and fell in love with him he's been
turned down for parau for eating a guard
oh my poor baby and I can't get a
conical visit that's so terrifying
Maniac love doesn't have to be a crime
like when you would write your name over
and over maniacally on a spiralbound
notebook in class just wishing he'd turn
around during algebra class and say do
you want to study tonight and then he's
so overwhelmed with passion when he sees
your pooms and then you hello am I on
heart um yes you are oh I couldn't tell
I was on hold forever and I heard some
pathetic woman weeping about her high
school algebra fantasy don't you
remember how unexperienced you were in
high school it was over in 3 seconds I
could never hold my own oh yeah maybe
for you do you have a question I just
can't meet the right person I want to
meet someone special I'll get off the
phone who's that your sister no that's
just my wife look I need to meet someone
really special ideally once a week in a
motel wearing leather speaking Germann
um that's great next caller hello jez
remember me I am Fernando martinz oh God
not you again look it was a mistake we
all get drunk at
funerals okay the heart can only takes
so much until it explodes or gets
clogged with tar from postp Passion
redwoods talk to you soon remember if
you're going to smoke in bed love is
like an ashtray butts one after another
you feel like [ __ ] afterwards and you
wake up with someone else's lighter
we'll see you next time on Lonely Hearts
no wonder these people are alone that
was lonely hearts opinions are free
which is why we're here it's news and
talk that our sponsors agree on
wct let's go find out what's really
happening in the world
news I'm Leanne for wct news we distort
you can't rort breaking news is
skateboarding turning your son gay also
San Fiero has been hit by one10 scale
chaos recently following a series of
many terrorist attacks tiny techn
terrorists are suspected more on that
story as it comes in a district attorney
is facing a long jail sentence after he
was arrested outside the vanol hotel
trying to escape with well over a ton of
marijuana police are currently
investigating claims it was for personal
use staying with pot police are
celebrating the destruction of a major
Hall of marijuana in Flint County
recently unfortunately the huge fire
caused problems for local Wildlife much
of which was found eating chocolate
listening to the same band over and over
and buying fractal artwork Richard Burns
is on the scene oh man I am wicked bab
hey man in the movie you got shot but
you look great baby hey who's the guy
with the antl oh [ __ ] no dude dude I was
just checking to see if she was in heat
no it's it's cool dude she's your do
dude be
cool all right inhabitants of bone
County reported further inexplicable
lights over the desert yeah sure did
government officials blame the water
supply and more positive news came from
Street good guy Big Smoke who today
unveiled his new orphanage in a ceremony
in Los Santos yes thank you thank you
I'd just like to say this is a great day
for the impoverished and disadvantage of
Los Santos and it's a real honor that I
am as generous as I am I remember when I
was a little boy my dear mother would
ask me what I wanted to be when I grew
up and I said Mom I want to be a savior
it's a great opportunity the Big Smoke
orphanage teaches kids important skills
I was an orphan I struggled I saw
friends make mistakes and get pulled
from the path of righteousness but now
thanks to the generosity of a great man
like me kids is going to be saved Big
Smoke baby remember the name in crime
news Asian gang trouble in San Fiero is
on the rise with problems developing
between Chinese Triad gangs and
Vietnamese gangs a government official
released this statement hey if they want
to kill each other let them it's great
it means your taxes go down I'm Leanne
for wct news stay
indoors you're good but let's be honest
you're not perfect and that's not
American we strive to be number one in
everything Sports politics economics
homelessness degeneracy Los Santos is
the home of beauty and glamour for the
whole world live up to society's
expectations Play Your Part your body is
a work of art don't leave it half
finished it's time for your creative
plastic surgery will'll make your face
as tight as a drum we'll suck fat out of
your body with an industrial pump
increase your confidence with fake
breasts to ensure people know what
you're all about for the more
adventurous why to try an extra nose or
three breasts you know how much men like
breasts can you imagine how Wild they'll
go for others my wife was complaining
that she did all the work carried the
baby for 9 months had painful labor it's
not fair to her my nipples are useless
that's why I Had Creative plastic
surgery I got a set of UDS installed now
my son can suck my UTS while I'm
watching the game the fellas at the bar
love them too men never stared
lasciviously at my ass then I had a tail
attached now people can't stop looking
Beauty Is Not skin deep it's less than
that creative plastic surgery achieve
your own
Utopia this is wct committed to bringing
you shows like the wild traveler even if
we received a ceent assist talk is cheap
especially on this station featuring
more Rich angry people complaining
wct cocka dooodle do it's time for
chicken COA dooodle do is time for a
feast eat a 90 piece bucket you can
tell he's toing Bell the chicken is a
bird with atin brain so we assume he
doesn't feel any pain we shrink their
heads and we breed them fast six wings
40 breasts then gas cocka doood do
psychotic crazy cocka dooodle do factory
farming insane we denied it all before
our St price fell come down to coling
Bell clucking Bell if you enjoy it the
chicken didn't die in vain the most
boring show with a brand new host
entertaining America with
llo welcome to entertaining America this
is llo I got to say it pardon me but uh
don't call it a comeback I've been here
for years just unemployed but I'm back
running the media got to love this West
Coast Vibe everybody here is so
laid-back and lazy I'm here with a man
who gets paid to talk for a living it's
incredible what a concept um he's called
a rapper oglock how are you oglock it's
OG Lo OG L you hear me player yes of
course I hear you you're only a few feet
away man listen I'm a big fan I I love
rap I I think I mean singing songs about
yourself that's awesome
H H how you living straight really are
you really straight what you going to
question me dude it's cool if somebody
passes it to me I don't ask questions
it's probably not laced anyway so who
out there wants to talk to OG Lok caller
you're on entertaining America I love
the way you rap about the Louisiana
Purchase straight you know the French
sold us Louisiana so we would have a
place to show our tits my point exactly
yeah we need more naked Liberty exactly
look I'm no rapper even though I dress
like one but I think I could really get
into you know getting hammered singing
about setting things on fire shooting up
funerals you know striking poses smoking
a lid exactly you see the Constitution
was written on reefa by dudes with
Whitten and teeth you see my clothing
company Lo down home of the G says this
I love reer it's the rules if you're a
rapper wow that sound like some great
rules you know you get a lot of flack in
the media these days at a recent press
conference your manager came to your
defense a lot of people say gangster rap
is misogynistic posturing by fake ass
idiots who spend more time in drama
school than they ever did pimping or
hustling dope well I assure you OG Lok
is the real thing he's hated women all
his life he soed drugs to school
children he's murdered innocent people
Just for kicks but he Rhymes Like An
Angel and I assure you it's all in a
good cause so either way you can feel
good about yourself listening to this
music well that was very informative Big
Smoke is doing a lot for the community
or or to it he sounds like a great guy
so I want to get in on this rap thing do
I have to break dance you know do the
windmill hey can you body poop come on
llo you know OG ain't no Playboy I ain't
down with that [ __ ] it ain't Gangsta I
walk the walk you know what I'm saying
fresh yo I'm I'm down I'm into walking
too but I was thinking maybe we could
have a breakoff you know I get spit on
my back you being funny I'm trying to be
watch it fool I warn you I got the
streets I got a rep me and my man smoke
we took over I've been gang banging
since I was three ice cold killer excuse
me gang banging I never understood that
I mean other guys in the room like I'm
ice cold [ __ ] don't make me dump on you
g I'm the streets man I am danger I'm
taking rap in a whole new direction from
now it's about making words rhyme and
I'm going Toe to Toe with you in a
minute why do you rappers get so worked
up you're rich You've Won stop shooting
at each other you know and you keep
saying I'm from the streets well you
know what dude everyone has a street in
front of their house that doesn't make
you cool oh we got a comedian huh you
got scratched huh [ __ ] you damn you
mock ass [ __ ] Punk trick Buster fool I
don't I don't know what you said but uh
he this ought to calm you down I brought
you some Malt Liquor you a bust of fool
lucky I don't handang you out the window
or turn you out cuz I'm also a pimp
including dudes I'll pimp anything you
hear me no dude I hear you loud and
clear man you will pimp anything listen
how many hot women need a man cuz I mean
it's kind of been a dream of mine to
sleep with housewives are you dissing my
ho [ __ ] no no no no dude uh your hoes
are [ __ ] your hoes are [ __ ] you a
buster what are you I'm a buster I'm a
buster what whatever that is dude put
put the gun away don't diss my strap I
love your strap you're a great gun look
I'm I'm just coming down off the80s
please don't shoot me homie relax fool
no one's getting dumped on I'm a warrior
poet I tell a caution every tale about
life on the streets you know only too
well that was OG Lok hey man it's been a
real pleasure straight yeah good luck
with the music hope you can make a
killing we'll see you next time maybe
I'll get to take some cers like I want
if wct wasn't holding me back man this
has been entertaining America with llo
peace and chicken grease so that's how
you're going to be entertained the news
and all the other things that really
matter to you like sensationalist
[ __ ] tired of all the sunshine and
good weather looking for a real American
vacation visit The Shining jewel in the
Rust Belt Crown Casa City it's a real
man's vacation the pride of a nation is
in Cara City it's steel ice and poverty
spend a ROM Mantic evening in the beauty
of the nighttime riverg glow at the
Flaming River Watch Real Men Who make
things lose their jobs and fight on our
special closing the-mill guided tour
come see what we're really made of this
is real America drunk proud unemployed
and angry hear the eagle Roar in Cara
City this is what the Heartland is all
about is the world ending we hope so we
need the ratings the news is
next Leanne for wct news news with the
bottom line in mind top news stories was
Moses really from Ohio chairs the silent
killer in your home now wct traffic and
Transit after months all bridges have
been reopened bone County Tiara Robata
and L venturus County are now linked up
with the rest of the state locals
celebrated by mass outbreaks of
xenophobia and inbreeding also police
are celebrating the removal of a major
crack cocaine ring by undercover police
that has virtually stopped the flow of
drug into Los Santos Richard spoke to a
man on the scene that's right Leanne
it's another victory for prohibition
police are really celebrating after this
one one officer told me his amazing true
life story of how he infiltrated a drug
ring and how cool it was to get paid to
get high yeah I was undercover smoking
crack every day you know just to be one
of them I even took my wife undercover
and made her a crack [ __ ] say hello to
the news man [ __ ] hey don't I know you
the rusty trombone right I doubt it
[ __ ] you're you're crazy back to you
Leanne police are struggling to solve
the mystery of a container ship found
deserted and full of bodies the FBI is
investigating and government officials
denied the existence of an area of bone
County that isn't on the map someone who
was unprepared to be Nam said the
so-called place that isn't called
anything doesn't exist and if it did
we'd name it something and where is mad
dog Wonder record exex the rapper has
battled alcoholism and egomania for many
years and recently missed a concert in
Las Venturas staying in venturus it used
to be a patch of desert then it was a
mob town now it's the corporate
headquarters of America Richard explains
from the streets that's right Leanne it
used to be a patch of desert then it was
a mob town now it is the corporate
headquarters of America back to you in
the studio in foreign news we have War
famine pestilence and a lot of Envy
aimed at our way of life stay at home
it's better that way I'm Leanne v wct
news stay alert they're after us this is
wellknown philanthropist Big Smoke and
you're listening to
wct make a difference to your community
keep our City's drug free look I'm doing
my bit how are you helping at home at
work or in rehab listen to
wct have you heard the number one
gardening show in San Andreas if not
here's what you're missing pesticides
exploring damp gopher holes my new
walk-in closet what's on your mind about
gardening tubers and and root vegetables
oh God not you again is it okay to cut
the eyes out of a potato and eat it well
why don't I come over and cut your eyes
out and eat you what a silly question if
you purchase the gardening with Maurice
calendar it's in the August section next
to the picture of the firefights and the
cute Pomeranian puppy yeah I bought that
calendar but on every page you're naked
and in a different Garden
and the guys at work make fun of me well
listen if you're ashamed of your human
body then keep your clothes on I am
blossoming in those pictures and I
wanted to capture it on film but I
happen to be proud of my human body as
much as I am proud of my flowers when
they are blossoming I like to take
pictures of them when I'm blossoming I
like to take pictures of it next caller
hi I live here in bone County and I
can't get nothing to grow have you had
any ch
I sure do I got seven kids and some of
them's got the same daddy well look
you've grown something little miniature
idiots that look like you move out of
the desert you [ __ ] I guess you're
right well thanks Maurice I am right and
I'm Maurice on gardening with Maurice
gardening with Maurice only on
wct area 53 is next don't say we didn't
warn you did the government recruit
school children to beat you up in school
School are goldfish really communist
spies I'm M Trill this is area 53 I'm
broadcasting live from my mobile home in
the desert I am telling you it's hot
like alien balls in here going to the
conspiracy lines hi my name's Adam first
I've been doing some much needed
surveillance in the desert while
hangliding I've noticed a peculiar
trailer compound where a man is running
around in a space suit conducting weird
rituals with domats what well he
probably wants you to leave him alone
get a real hobby like pretending to be
someone on TV next caller hey it's me
again you now come on man tell the
people about the desert how come there's
something missing huh a map with things
missing ain't a real map and that's what
they feed us that and female hormones
and a water supply yeah I hear you on
that one well I'll call back when I got
proof you better not be tracing this
call I don't trace calls everything in
life should be anonymous I tell my
various partners that all the time Rick
from blueberry Acres what do you think
klam I couldn't have said it better
myself crun truth is wisdom brother and
brother wisdom works that's why we made
it up you and I have a lot in common
Vivian is calling in from carser City
and wants to talk about crop circles oh
wow I never thought I'd actually make it
on the show is that because you have a
girl's name well here's a conspiracy
your mom hates you holy [ __ ] how'd you
know that next caller my name is Neil I
got to a lot of demonstrations to pick
up religious pamphlets none of them say
anything about about the aliens try
reading between the lines and if that
doesn't work do some then you'll
understand all about the aliens and just
where you were planted Mike online 10
man I think my dentist is attracted to
me she knocks me unconscious and has her
way with me and it's unlikely but it
could be true my teeth feel great but I
feel icky all dirty and used like a sex
object I'll tell you what makes me feel
icky the fact I haven't washed in two
months whatever you do trust nobody next
caller I am a domesti my name is 63 23
69439 well that's not a very original
name I didn't know robots listen to this
show we know what you are doing do my
domestic B brothers and Fister enough of
that little guy sounds like he's been
programmed for evil all right let's get
to the real meat and potatoes newsmen
lying to our face about weather balloons
historians ignoring my proof that ww 2
didn't happen the FDA infiltrated by the
very device they're supposed to regulate
the plug mind control devices but we'll
have to leave that for now you are
leaving area 53 you've been abducted
until next time stay alert they're after
you you're leaving area 53 check your
rectum the news and all the other things
that really matter to you like people
dying lady on fire bodies everywhere and
explosions is hanging from the trees
this accident is really cool
[Music]
wct hello uh hey it's me Jonathan I I
don't know it Jonathan yeah that's the
name they gave me at the orphanage after
you put me up for adoption how could you
give me away bring the family together
again San Andrea's telephone for those
difficult conversations if you're into
exploring exotic places and forbidden
fruit stay tuned it's the wild traveler
next hello hello I'm James pistan World
traveler and this is the wild traveler
from Peru to San Andreas in 8 Days by
balloon often while lounging around
Garden parties we forget the brave
workers worldwide who toil day and night
for the products we consume some are
even so dedicated to our happiness they
carry products in balloons shoved inside
themselves to be a balloon
floating
mesmerizing we go to the phones yes we
do I can't believe you actually
recommended we go to Barbados on our
honeymoon it was revolting there were
poor people I live in Vinewood to be
away from poor people Barbados is lovely
look I want to be very clear I'm not
racist just careful okay I like
allinclusive Resorts where you can drink
as much as you want be around other
people from San Andreas and the only
interaction you have with the locals is
if you need a cocktail or or some spice
in the bedroom with your husband well
that's sounds lovely with people like
you it's no wonder we don't bother
curing cancer next caller you're on the
wild
traveler yeah it's funny you go on and
on about other countries but you live
here America rules you commie eat me
well we've been trying Tom you're on the
line I'm so sick of England oh let's go
to the pub they're all alcoholics at
least we drink a 24 pack in private
instead of hanging on some social
setting making a fool of ourselves
people say it's so civilized in Europe
they got thousands of years of History
well I saw a movie about Europe once and
I was disgusted I mean people still
defecate in their living rooms and cover
it up with dirt like a cat you can't
find a decent turlet anywhere or a good
chicken wing and a strippers overcharge
good lord your Philistine you should
stay out of England I hear there is a
casino invent shers that is just like
the rest of the world only with better
toilets and full of morons like you do
you want culture or do you want safety
it's your choice personally I want
irrigation of the colonic variety but
that's a whole different story and it is
early let's go to the phones who's on
the phones no one come on call up
anyone it wouldn't be like this in Peru
I can tell you there I once made a phone
call with 30 boys sitting on my lap not
because I paid them they wanted to be
there or in Marley where nobody knows
what a phone is and a lot of people have
never even heard of plastic surgery or
the [ __ ] theme park there the glory
holes aren't theme parks I can tell you
it's violent and bloody and authentic
what are you scared of you wimps give me
a call someone please hello you're on
wild traveler where are you I'm on a
cliff how romantic I want to jump I know
what you mean jump into the unknown how
can it be a sin if it feels good anyway
what's your question why am I here I
don't know why are you there where are
you Kenya no I'm in verdant Bluffs loome
place I'd jump if I were you I want to
go to hell me too buy a refrigerator
magnet when you get there on with the
show any callers
no okay maybe I should hit the travel
log again this is from my diary in Sri
Lanka for a few rupees a day I have
employed the services of a young man who
has been my guide and pleasure as well
as travel there is something very exotic
about him ainda he could be a boy but
like many locals in certain lights he
looks just like a little girl he is a
real MX who knows exactly what he is
doing to be Oh wrong page here we are
ainda took me deep into jungle and there
we took part in an ancient write of
passage for adolesence on the cusp of
adulthood we hunted each other in game
very similar to the ancient games of
kiss Chase I used to play no wrong
page ainda has left me I'm broken I
thought I meant something but it seems
he would rather become a fisherman than
follow me in an exotic life of
degeneracy and narcotics as my house boy
I hate myself why does this keep
happening to me hell wrong bit again
where's the page about watching the
elephants mate and it being really
disturbing and making me slightly
jealous for both parties hey has someone
been stealing Pages out of my journal my
producer is jealous he keeps stealing my
stuff and lending it to people just last
week I heard him saying government
agents wanted to look at it what a load
of trash ah we have a call finally I
just want to tell people about a great
holiday you mean vacation we call it
vacation what is it searching for a yeti
in the Himalayas learning to play an
Alpine horn hunting for pythons in
Africa Oh Canada but what about a young
man to peel grapes what about fine local
herbs hey it's cheap and it's plentiful
apart from the rent boys what about the
food poisoning what about the starving
Beggars what about the political
instability and the chance to eat
insects I don't want foreign have you
seen the news lately Philistine well if
you want exotic go to Hawaii they still
trade in beads there and ride planks
rather than motorboats time for me to
head south again on the next show we'll
be discussing
Amsterdam Paradise regained
Morocco squidy smoke until next time
travel safe Chow Bella I'm James piston
and this has been the wild
traveler this is wct committed to
bringing you shows like the wild
traveler even if we received a season
assist let's head over to The Newsroom
lean for wct news reporting what the
morning memo tells us to pornography in
preschool the sickening shortage and
shiny compact discs turning your
children into Killers plus the Epsilon
Tract a psychotic underground power
hungry cult running the government and
Vinewood or an idea whose time has come
the wct team spoke to one member
whenever I'm in trouble I talk to my
invisible friends when I was a kid my
mother told me to be good or invisible
people would kill me I'm passing that
terrifying living along to my children
like virus also police are investigating
the murder of Liberty City crime family
the synos whose bodies were found in a
meat factory in Las venturus could this
be the start of a mafia war or was it a
sick game gone hideously wrong either
way America's beef producers say it will
all blow over Los Santos police officers
Frank Tenpenny and Eddie palaski are
being sought by government officials in
order to stand trial for the murder of
Officer Ralph pendelbury the pair whom
prosecutors claim have masterminded a
huge huge criminal organization have
disappeared LSPD spokespeople said they
were undercover Las venturus was
recently celebrating the opening of the
four dragons Casino a huge new pleasure
palace with a Chinese feel setting a new
level of optimistic debauchery for the
country Richard reports from venturus
where the four dragons hosted the child
actor convention who do you have the
[ __ ] to get a free drink in this place
how do you stay 14 when the Dealer's
showing 12 you [ __ ] yeah hit me Richard
Leanne as you know actors are a shallow
and insecure lot often uncomfortable
with their sexuality but what's worse
are child actors especially when they
get together Jimmy from the canceled
sitcom just the five of us was dragged
out by police earlier today this is
[ __ ] hey don't arrest my [ __ ] I
am a star it's just flower I swear Jimmy
I'm Richard Burns wct news what do you
think of my five uncles the show that
replaced yours what do you think dumbass
that show sucks my ass and why do you
still look like a kid I'm 51 years old I
just look like a kid I'm going to [ __ ]
punch you hey how do you like that you
liberal media bastard Richard Burns wct
news back to you Leanne I'm Leanne for
wct news I wouldn't sleep if I were you
the tight end zone is next brought to
you by logger beer and Redwood
cigarettes a game just isn't a game if
you're not drunk and coughing one
two godam I think I just [ __ ] my pants
you're now in the tight end zone if
someone's playing with a ball or two
we're there to talk about it I'm your
host Derek fery today on the Big Show
clearing out more housing projects for
golf courses girls in skirts and we
revisit the Rivalry the Rivalry That
Never Dies Liberty City [ __ ] and
beavers going at it again love it loath
it by the Jersey eat the junk food call
it Athletics I'm Derek zaker grab your
balls and run cuz someone is going to
pin you to the ground and give it up the
you
nowhere Winner Takes all including the J
A warts who is on the line why don't you
boys ever talk about the real issue in
sports today the loss of tradition I
wore a leather helmet playing football
the left side of my face is paralyzed
but it was worth it we won the game I
mean my boy goes to high school right
and he's actually given a choice of
different sports to play and there's
only one sport I know it's ruining this
country's traditions and history I mean
I want him to be a big sports star so I
don't have to work no more and he can
afford all the drugs and hookers he
wants and he's only gone and started
playing lacrosse ooh look at me I'm
carrying my bag on a stick and wearing a
skirt might as well teach my boy to hunt
butterflies okay I guess you're right or
wrong it all depends how you look at
things any race fans out there hey any
football fans suck fans go home we don't
want you here your game is terrible and
we don't win at it next caller hi Derek
my name's Cole and I'm a big racing fan
I tell you that where I'm from there's
nothing more excited than getting
shitfaced and going death in 110° heat
and watching cars go in a circle for
several hours yeah yeah hey I think
that's what it's all about H that and
putting a lot of stickers on your car
buddy yeah that really gets on my nerves
I mean I'm a bald man my wife left me
because of it and half the cars are
sponsored by baldness remedies castron
team racing yeah wasn't the name of my
mother's cat is that all about I mean
racing teams should be sponsored by
things that are familyfriendly like hard
liquor or cigarettes not the reason my
wife ran off with that cop what hey
screw your wife pal probably a lot of
guys
did this ain't Lonely Hearts I mean
let's stop showering each other in
Golden sports drink and get get this
ball back in play Hello caller Derek
that caller talking about the bathon
it's sick I tell you and unnatural this
town has never been the same since they
had the Olympics here years ago kids
fling a javelins like ancient Greeks
people running with burning torches
throwing hammers what kind of man wakes
up in the morning and says I'm going to
go throw hammers for a living ooh the
long jump look at me I can jump really
high great I have a gun want to fight
it's distracting us from our Primal urge
to paint your face with war paint whip
yourself into a sweaty C iotic fzy and
then go annihilate and hospitalize
complete strangers then you bang a bimbo
on the
sidelines bang bang bang look I loved
High School football and I love
gymnastics hey Jack from Idlewood in L
Santos yeah how come you don't talk
about the best sport of all horse racing
I mean tiny angry people on horses how
can you go wrong I don't ride anything
bigger than me you know what I'm saying
I mean that's why I never in a rodeo man
I mean first off why would you ride a
bull go find a big girl they they they
they could use the attention and and
that's all we have time for okay hey I'm
Derek zakary till next time Play Safe
People Go baby go
team you're listening to wct or maybe
you aren't maybe you became so offended
that the tight end zone has no female
callers that you change stations I know
I would and have I'm not here anymore
pompus I'm running on air I'm walking on
clouds I don't exercise I don't care
pompus I paid top dollar for these
incredible high technology polyester
shoes to walk around the mall and shop
for more sports equipment I won't play
sports in I need to get more from Life
much more I need to get high really high
high on
air oh yeah these aish shoes really pump
up that's right you can now buy some air
the science of sports and marketing
results in a shoe that pumps sound silly
to you what if we told you that eras
pump up would improve your game by 300%
but I don't have a game you got to have
game be a winner pump up and slam
dunk oh yeah God the size of your shoes
you'll shave seconds off your personal
best oh yeah you mean I can whack off
even more times a day po absolutely
probably five times more because you'll
be walking on air you'll feel so much
more athletic after pumping up your
shoes you'll automatically lose weight
and feel Hightech just like the sports
stars you are a star now you're winner
with air in his shoes now I can reach
for the stars I've pumped up my
ego Pump It Pump It Up with
Aris turn over in case you learn
something the news is next lean for wct
news unfair and skewed for you in the
top stories everyone is trying to kill
you but at least you're not in prison
yet disgraced movie star Jack Howitzer
broke his silence recently following his
onair murder of radio host Billy Dexter
facing trial and a possible death
sentence howitz are spoke to Richard
wctr would like to be clear we did pay
for this interview that's right Leanne I
am Richard Burns here in Los Santos
prison as we all know since politicians
stopped musicians from coming here to
sing songs about shooting your woman on
drugs everyone is now questioning their
sexuality Jack Howitzer you're facing a
death sentence how do you feel about
that I broke out of a p camp in Korea
all right so I'll be out of here soon uh
correct me if I'm wrong but I believe
that was a movie and it wasn't real oh
no it was real I'm a veteran of over 40
films but I've got a different hoochi
now say hello to the newsman hoi um
hello you want me to kill you like the
last hoochi say it like an Asian girl uh
hello how are you wow Jack Howitzer that
is a fine prison [ __ ] where can I get
one of those Richard BD burs wct news
the trial of allegedly disgraced police
officers Frank ten Penney and Eddie
palaski began yesterday although Mr
palaski was not at court personally
prosecutors maintain both are guilty of
murder racketeering drug running and
sexual offenses defense maintained
officers were just doing their job
government officials are denying any
knowledge of black helicopters that were
recently seen flying over the state
black helicopters what black helicopters
that clear CLE it up a Los venturus
institution Caligula forced to admit
that it was recently robbed it's the
first major Heist carried out on a
venturus casino in 30 years government
officials are not ruling out Foul Play
meanwhile no explanation has been
forthcoming as to why the Sherman Dam
stopped generating electricity for a few
hours recently one bystander blamed
aliens who drink electricity before
deflowering virgins I'm Leanne for wct
news it's going to get worse trust me
your home is your castle and like most
castles there's always the worrisome
less fortunate trying to storm the gates
no longer at executive Intruder
extermination service will'll ensure
that you'll live in a fortress and live
your life WorryFree with my vindictive
and backstabbing personality I always
knew I'd be successful but there's a
price to pay money gives me freedom
freedom to be scared of things that
normal people don't have to worry about
when it comes to people trying to get a
buck off me or come knocking I turn to
outside help your home will be
surrounded by only the best security
equipment razor wire Doberman landmines
night vision and motion sensors and if a
stranger or unwanted relative should
make it inside all of your doors will be
wired with bombs but what about when my
children need to go to school your
children will be equipped with
bulletproof vests and depending on if
they attend public school stun guns and
mace when you're successful nobody wants
to be bothered I'll Slaughter anyone who
even thinks of harming my family with
executive Intruder extermination service
they do it for me call today for your
free home demonstration the world is a
dangerous place for you it doesn't have
to be enjoy listening to mental patience
area 53 is next is your child really an
alien has the future already happened
somewhere else and finally is cheese the
latest weapon in a battle against
communism we explore deeper much deeper
I'm Marvin Trill this is area 53 prepare
to be a PO hello yes hello I would like
to talk about a conspiracy okay it's
starts with food and our toxic culture
these chemicals and our bodies you must
flush them out Marvin first start by
masticating did you say masturbating
listen again Marvin am I lising here
masticating vigorously to really cleanse
you're going to have to do some yoga the
cleansing properties of doing yoga with
a garden hose up your ass cannot be
exaggerated Marvin it's time for your
down dog to really have a tail I was
wondering when my career would hit
bottom and now it's here right before my
eyes Stewart is on the line I think
everyone out there will agree that the
Russians are in charge now foreigners
are behind that exoro handheld gaming
device to decrease our productivity and
make our thumbs useless so our kids
can't fire machine guns I hear what
you're saying about video games people
are dying every day of malaria and it's
all because of the messages planted in
our minds from that degenatron in the80s
line 18 hello okay man I warned you I've
been over to the other side what are you
talking about Buddy I've been inside
inside everything seen everything
remember the first time you did
mushrooms there are aliens living in the
state aliens and I've held them in my
own hand everybody go to the desert beg
their forgiveness and how do you know
all this I went to the camp believe what
you want to believe but ask yourself why
should I make this up the only thing I
want to ask myself is how I can keep you
off future shows oh God Kevin hello
you're on the air all the missiles are
under my control not the government's
control why do you think they put me in
solitary confinement for 8 months
because I can can launch nuclear
missiles by just whistling into a phone
really great could you wipe out all the
other radio stations in town for me hey
I don't do that anymore I only use my
powers for good ah look this isn't a
cartoon or TV show let's get real for a
second the problem with people like you
who have superpowers is that you really
don't use them for good if I had
superpowers everyone would be naked and
women signing autographs at conventions
couldn't resist me all right going to
the conspiracy line yeah this this is
Montag okay my name's Montag oh yes yes
I got that hey have you ever leveled a
house with a helicopter yeah know but
that'd be really cool I thought you were
a DJ you used to talk more about killing
people with helicopters I prefer
electric cable tightly wound around
people's throats watching them go blue
in the face we have a lot of Aerospace
fans and plenty of murderers who like
the show inside I feel like it's time to
close the pod bay door and take a rest
until next time reset your memory chip
at don't don't believe what they tell
you this is Marvin Trill you're leaving
area 53 klam be
careful that was area 53 where reality
is an alien concept if you crave News
wct West Coast talk
[Music]
radio sounds like you got a nasty cough
yeah no [ __ ] here baby try this soothe
yeah soothe annihilates cough and cold
symptoms
wow I'm seeing
donkeys that's the patented cough
killing concoction of Codine morphine
and alcohol your cold will be history
how's your cold now who the hell are you
I'm your wife fool sooth kills a cough
fast and for the kid's chesty cough it's
Soo junr the medication that comes in a
fun animal-shaped container kids will
love hey look at me I'm bigal medication
just like
Dad oh my God he's B PR no that that's
just the medicine doing his magic thanks
to sooth his cough is history with sooth
you'll forget you had a cough your name
or where to properly go to the bathroom
feel better fast with
soothe now it's the couple who each
thinks the other is screwing America I
say you say is next with the
Phillips I'm Dr Phillips and I'm a
liberal get to a 10-step program that's
12 steps yeah you only deserve 10 I'm
also Dr Phillips and I'm conservative
today on the show is it okay to talk to
people we were at war with once and the
skyrocketing price of buying off a
politician and we talk to people without
Healthcare who are genuinely happy not
to be burdened with it it's political
debate and discussion from the right and
the wrong side of the track let's go to
the phones before right-wing anger
engulfs my wife who's on the line hi I
have an eating disorder so I like move
to the West Coast no that's so sad maybe
you need a support group with some
caring friends yeah maybe you should
keep your finger out of your throat and
eat a donut 99% of of the world wake up
each day and E dirt and queen puke a lot
here can't keep a meal down boohoo what
do you expect sympathy this is Los
Santos people would give their right arm
and left leg to live here it's Paradise
but you have to suffer to belong you
can't take the heat get out of the
nuclear reactor next caller yeah uh I
agree with that caller about the nuclear
plant next to the projects you know
Nature has a way of taking care of poor
people tornadoes don't like poor people
right like I don't do laundry I'm
liberated independent and I have three
maids all of them on less than minimum
wage I mean poor people are so happy to
work for me especially when I help them
unionize uh do you have a question sort
of hey you know I got the same name as
you yeah pton oh well it's a family name
no Mary I was called Bruce by my parents
but I prefer Mary it's much more yeah
feminine no biblical which like okay I'm
an atheist but I love the Bible I have
aund that I took from hotel rooms what's
your question well as a mother and a
fireman I was wondering what you guys
thought about diversity in America it
makes me very nervous well you see I'm
heavily into diversity I'm like a a man
with a womb lactating yes I think you're
a little confused no you're the one
that's confused I'm the one who eats
Alaskan salmon and children from Alabama
I speak English I eat German food I
practice French adultery and I weigh as
much as Vatican City I'm an American
okay you're a nut get off our show Mary
would you please stop eyeing the
producer I already slept with him so did
I O Brian's on the line hello Brian hi
my name's Brian I work at cigalus casino
in Las Venturas excellent you take
stupid people's money I love it very
capitalist hey Brian what's your concern
I did really well in the 80s but the
'90s are proving to be a real drag the
music is terrible the recession is
kicking my ass everyone I know is giv up
recreational drug use and the president
is doing my head in the 80s were really
a materialistic time I know I'm a
shallow person drown me look we need a
movie star to be president it works
they're the best Liars they do it
professionally well so do all
politicians next caller yeah I want to
talk about deforestation yes that is a
shame what they're doing to the thick
beautiful redwoods North of San Vio I
was talking about women but you're right
Sano is half the problem it ain't
natural and it's unamerican look
infatuation and disillusionment is the
American way but it works just look at
places without professional wrestling in
porno porno is the exploitation of women
some people want to be exploited like
Factory workers others want to be
degraded I mean really really degraded
like a liberal having his way with you
god it makes me feel so dirty talk more
slowly please dear moving swiftly on
from my wife you're an I say you say and
what's your question yeah this is Brad
I'm really into pleasuring myself good
grief well that's my business but I feel
discriminated against not only can I not
practice my hobby in the privacy of my
own Garden or car but my movies are
rated as
pornographic I mean let me ask you a
question thre sums right well that's
where our problem started yeah the
producer well right I ran a movie with
two chicks and a dude and it's called a
porno people look at me like I'm some
sort of creep but it's natural but I
rent a movie with two dudes and a chick
it's all in French probably wins awards
called an art housee love triangle but
it's revolting no you're revolting get
the airwaves and into therapy buddy oh
that's the problem with men you're
imbeciles and yet you married me God
don't rub it in I did I was desperate
that's all we have time for luckily this
show is headed downhill when you take
the worst qualities of an elephant and a
donkey you get a lot of [ __ ] we'll see
you next time on I say you say you said
you like me in that donkey suit
jackass I say you say is heard only on
wct be thankful next up the reason
you're afraid the news Leanne for wct
news reporting what makes the
administration happy today's top stories
do trees cause baldness is noise the new
silent enemy of your family and a
special report on France one nation's
obsession with standup toilets breaking
wct news Navy officials are denying that
a hydrop plane was stolen from a Marine
Amphibious assault ship recently despite
eyewitness reports to the contrary
taxpayers on the scene are not happy I
pay my taxes that jet is supposed to be
bombing school and the FBI is
investigating possible links between the
massacre of farelli family members and
the slaying of the sndo family
unconfirmed reports suggest a similar
style of execution was used in both hits
an official commented it could be a
wormhole in space I'm Leanne for wct
news don't turn it off trust
me the most boring show with a brand new
host entertaining America with llo
welcome to entertaining America on wct
with me llo so the media you may hate us
but I got to tell you we hate ourselves
more and stop accusing us of being
liberal what a load of crap this station
is owned by ammunation I mean have you
ever heard anyone complain about guns on
this station hosts are getting shot by
them all the time but it just gets
glossed over but it also means I I now
have a job if you're afraid of your
mortality and never want to die here's
the solution it's a man who's got all of
America talking with his unique approach
to spiritual matters he's helped
thousands or so the Press pack tells me
Chris forage founder of the Epsilon
program is here hello Chris klam brother
brother what does that mean man so
epsilonism is it a load of crap or is it
the future well what do you think llo I
don't know well I mean I I I grow my own
religion is why I don't know it's I'm
kind of spaced out I mean but you guys
run around chanting lip bomb it's klom
well whatever both sound addictive to me
you know only popular people are
addicted to either let's go to the
phones hey Chris Epsilon sounds awesome
but if you read the fossil records
hunter gatherer dudes had it made I mean
who wouldn't want to drag their women
around by their hair they smoked
anything they could find that's like so
freaking cool then all the men would
like disappear for days at a time and
you'd only hear Beast shrieking in the
distance you know I went to a museum
once that guy got a point points are
irrelevant llo let me ask you something
do you want to be happy llo what kind of
question is that yes obviously then why
do you marck the happiness of others
well I mean this is Vinewood we're all
supposed to be like psychotic and Dogg
eat dog and you know bang your best
friend's wife I mean I'm with that last
guy we all have a primitive side there
Chris I mean you should have heard the
music I used to like in the'80s it was
it was hysterical what's hysterical
about being descended from from a sponge
and not knowing it what's funny about
being told that the world is millions of
years old when in fact it's only 157
years old fact and its age does not
change there's nothing funny about that
it's just weird you know that voice of
yours man holy [ __ ] I can believe
anything you say my time has come llo
and so has yours if if you let it um
well you know that that sounds good to
me hey wait are you going to try to sign
me up for the military that happened
once before I mean I'm into killing
people and I can say I'm cry when I'm
done killing and then there listen my
friend you can mock but I know the truth
about you I can see past your jokes into
that scared little boy beneath you you
my friend like a lot of other people are
being lined to I totally agree with you
finally inversion therapy I owe my mom a
huge apology listen pick a new set of
Lies mine are better let me ask you
something when did you last get laid llo
speaking of Lies wait look I'm not an
egg I got laid this morning by twins
whoa they each laid an egg and I formed
out of them what are you talking about
great a horny cult leader with a
breakfast fixation I love it you know
I'm thinking of a cult centered around
grits oh wait I'm sorry there already is
one in it's called the south for the
last time this is not a cult llo it's a
fellowship of like-minded adults who
tithe money in exchange for salvation
and merit badges every single thing we
do is voluntary including the swinging
and making things up why is this whole
town obsessed with
swinging let's go to the phones hey llo
love the show man hey I really love to
make out with hot chicks in church
perfect join us we've put a price on
salvation and it's a price worth paying
believe me look if you crave sexual
Conquest family betrayal class Warfare
and really feeling like you are a part
of something then just do it just do it
it's so easy join the Epsilon
group Chris stop trying to recruit
people I mean you even say you just make
this stuff up let's go to the phones hi
la llo ah Darius Fontaine look I told
you to leave me alone look look it was
an unfortunate incident that happened to
your mother but I was quite clear
grandmother not mother it's your fault
it doesn't work I nearly went to prison
man what you told me to do is illegal in
Most states whatever look Chris forage
is a liar and a cheat he made it up it
doesn't help anyone apart from him the
fact is people need to face their fears
remember I always say that face your
fears Don't Run Away Darius Fontaine can
kill my ass oh you you'd like that would
would you like that I don't think so and
I'll tell you why because you are the
devil people aren't really afraid you
know yet you make them kill their
families fears have to be faced that's
what I always say just ask llo hey don't
bring me into this Ruckus Darius this is
between you two guacos I mean and you
stay away from me Darius I've got a
restraining order dude llo the only way
that you can really communicate with
your ancestor aners is to pay someone
like me just a second I want you to try
something touch my cane this whole town
man I I think you've seen too many
movies dude you can be happy listen join
us be famous find your true self have a
breast nose surgery whatever you want
lie with nine new partners a week it
explains everything if there are no
women make them from sand from garbage
out of thin there the rich cry too low
well that's an interesting theory that
sounds like it was formulated with
Pharmaceuticals but you know I would
like to find about being rich and crying
cuz right now I'm just poor and crying
but this is the West Coast you know I'm
only in a lesbians man it's Destiny
Vinewood only lets you down in the
Epsilon program there are no series
finales it goes on and on and on we
don't abandon you H well we're going to
have to abandon this show great my first
show when a dude nearly kills me now I'm
being harassed by a former sociology
professor and an alcoholic turned self
deifying cultist please I got to get
back to the east coast this has been
entertaining America with llo on wct
culturally this country is flatlining
now you know why your home is your
castle and like most castles there's
always the worrisome less fortunate
trying to storm the gates no longer an
executive Intruder extermination service
we'll ensure that you'll live in a
fortress and live your life WorryFree
with my vindictive and backstabbing
personality I always knew I'd be
successful but there's a price to pay
money gives me freedom freedom to be
scared of things that normal people
don't have to worry about when it comes
to people trying to get a buck off me or
come knocking I turn to outside help
your home will be surrounded by only the
best security equipment razor wire Dober
mins landmines night vision and motion
sensors and if a stranger or unwanted
relative should make it inside all of
your doors will be wired with bombs but
what about when my children need to go
to school your children will be equipped
with bulletproof vests and depending on
if they attend public school stun guns
and mace when you're successful nobody
wants to be bothered I'll Slaughter
anyone who even thinks of harming my
family with executive Intruder
extermination service they do it for me
call today for your free home
demonstration the world is a dangerous
place for you it doesn't have to
be breaking wct news we go to Richard in
Los
Santos dude I am shitfaced Le
Los Santos is in Flames this Riot is
spectacular man I mean I can't even
describe it storefronts are being
smashed everywhere there is some great
stuff to be had there is free beer for
everybody dude I've been loading up this
is capitalism as it was meant to be baby
hey hey get away from my news van yeah
that's right I'm packing H I'm Richard
burds [ __ ] uh police advisor state of
Martial law has been declared you should
stay in your home senators are burning
the Constitution blah blah bity blo blah
blah blah I'm Richard Burns
wct
news Jimmy Jimmy get me some more beer
out of the back of the van and clear out
some space we're going to get ourselves
a big screen we'll keep you posted now
back to regular programming
hello Lisa yeah how you doing [ __ ] how
do you like living in that house we
built together huh do our kids like
watching that bald bastard if a new
husband kiss you in the morning they
want their real father Lisa when you
just can't be there in person San
Andrea's telephone for those difficult
conversations lonely it's about to get
much worse Lonely Hearts is next I'm
Christy McIntyre and this is lonely
hearts Hearts you know when we get
dumped or momed eyes it's really a good
thing because really I want you to
listen to me pull over I said pull over
life is not a game Life Is Love first
callar jez remember me I told you leave
me alone sometimes the heart is
confusing lady so is the brain you talk
too much if you look out the window you
will notice your car is on on fire oh my
God Fernando is back women know nothing
about
love this is why I am here Fernando
grows tired of hearing women on the
radio with bad device because if you
close your eyes you can be loving anyone
especially when you are alone on an
airplane bathroom and people are
knocking on the door and you keep
flushing and flushing let's take a goer
whose heart is on the line love is
finally in the air hi I love the show
I'm in a great mood my mistress just got
her period I love that day anyway I love
my wife I have 18 children and why you
have so many children are you a man with
a fire in his loins and a hole in his
Johnny well I can't really talk about
that I'm passing on a tradition raising
little soldiers SK you sound like you
enjoy a fetal position and sucking your
thumb wow how'd you know I always know
it's fine Fernando loves to suck his too
it's so hot and sexy people love
yourself first and then focus on others
you are number one your spouse is number
two and in the ultimate scenario they're
number three and number two comes from
Las Ventura's phone book after you see
Fernando's ad in the classified maybe we
leave that for now Amigos line eight
Daisy you're on the new and improved
Lonely Hearts Fernando Martinez speaking
of number two I totally love my
boyfriend but like the skid marks I
don't know what to do yes cars and bants
have a lot in common a real man leaves
his Mark like a stallion but I mean I
smell it but I don't say anything and he
just rolls down the window and acts like
it's all cool well it's not cool why do
men have this problem Fernando learned
this years ago while playing emotional
Music Inside every great man is a
wounded little boy full of fire fire
from his ass climbing trees blowing up
frogs beating up slow classmates
sleeping with your friends all in the
day's work it is life it is love it is
better than warts I think on the mind of
line for is a guy who calls himself
Carpenter Chris hell yeah I'm a
carpenter I drink all day and nail 2x4s
oh yes little people need love more than
anyone I have one client who calls me
all the time the girls complain he's
stuck in the 70s let's take another call
Fernando is in charge riding the phone
like a jeap Floy line six hi I've got a
very extensive pornography collection it
takes up the whole house what does that
say about me it says what somebody
should say maybe I say it listen to
Fernando there is nothing like the real
thing it is so silly to spend hundreds
of dollars on vide tapes of people
making passion when you can make the
tapes yourself and sell them and make
money let Fernando heal you like a
chiropractor but not as creepy and
addictive hello Frank from Foster Valley
I wish my dog could talk and cuddle me
all night Jewel stay away from animals
it's it's not legal not even for me it
is not moral maybe someday I set up a
petting suit for people like you when
you want to understand the connection
that keeps us on this planet since the
dinosaurs when the passion burns like a
nasty itch when fate caed you to leave a
town after an incident or the risk of a
father shotgun is fate an incident is a
five alarm fire an incident I come to
Las Venturas a city with more love that
it can handle love is realizing your
calling I say this I once play music
that brings back pass but I realize you
can have even more passion with a credit
card people in venturus only care about
slap machines yes maybe you pull the
handle and win the backdoor passion it
is different with every woman some women
need the soft tush because they have
been traumatized others have already
been traumatized so you treat them like
a truck driver and steal a six-pack on
your way out what are you talking about
I am talking about passion I am talking
about romance hey let me back in it's my
show no I teach you how to talk in just
a second to be quiet goodbye ladies and
gentlemen it is so good to teach you
about love s Andreas you in your car tou
yourself I love you all christe I will
be out in five wear something Slinky but
sophisticated and trashy your heart is
no longer lonely Fernando has been here
this was lonely hearts get out of here
you creep oh my God is that bush cologne
you're wearing yes that is Bush colog do
you like that and do you like this this
is Fernando's signature move
Fernando that L passion is amazing oh
wow that's inel let me see that I I love
taco let me see that taco pleas give it
to me
fando that was lonely hearts only on
wct talk is cheap especially on this
station featuring more Rich angry people
complaining w
TTR and now the number one show for
vegetables on the radio gardening with
Maurice okay we are back in the garden
I'm Maurice and we must answer Nature's
call going to the phones greetings
Garden lover what's your name hi my name
is Trish okay is that short for Patricia
uh yeah oh then what I asked is what
your name was not the nickname your skin
head boot wearing friends call you at
the rallies maybe you should do less
drugs and learn to try a bit harder next
caller hi my name is Colleen and my
husband has a topiary problem o this
sounds serious well he started off small
scale just recreational usage you know
doing horses and [ __ ] RS the odd unicorn
but it's kind of gotten out of control h
how so he just can't stop I mean people
think it's all fun and games but what
happens when the party stops what
happens then okay just just hold the
phone hold the phone and get a grip okay
at my house when the party stops we pay
the [ __ ] get rid of the sailors and 15
Men start crying in unison well that's
your business my husband's reached
bottom it's terrible giraffes Lions
elephants rhinos all of them carved out
of Hedges Penguins dogs Velociraptors
you name it he's made a leafy version
what could be more natur natural than a
man trimming a hedge into the shape of
an animal very therapeutic makes a man
feel like a god when you can twist
nature to your own perverse
entertainment then you know we've won
eat me Darwin but now he's trimming
bushes into a spaceship a rocket and a
lance he runs around with hedge clippers
and screams trim that bush at our
neighbors he even fashioned a shrub into
a kangaroo with a pouch and he sweeps
inside it nights oh he's freaking out on
Bush he needs help please you got to
help me I hate Hedges well the Romans
love topiary and look at their
contributions to society but as they say
if the grass is green or in the other
Fella's yard then you bang his college
son when the dad's out of town okay next
caller whoops hold on a second I'm
blossoming there we go all done my
name's Henry I are you blossoming I uh I
guess I am I've really come into my own
in the past few months since I joined a
cult and began tithing money in exchange
for Spiritual happiness and letting
everyone take turns on my wife anyway I
have a lovely Garden mostly carnivorous
plants a venus fly trap reminds me of my
mother she's in prison now anyway it's
so fascinating how it catches animals
and eats them I started with flies and
now mine can swallow a whole squirrel or
a small horse if I C it in half first
have you tried any experiments on human
beings yeah I've been working on that
good man good man see the secret of
nature is once something is at the
height of beauty and potential it is
time for it to wither and die a bit like
the British Empire cuz look at that
whole place withering and dying right
before our eyes it's run by a queen and
if she had a pistol she'd be the king
luckily in this country we don't know
the meaning of the word hubris but hell
I'm all over the place here it's so easy
to get out of control when you're doing
something that comes natural line two
you're on gardening with muries yeah my
name is Terence can I call you Telly
Welly uh sure I I guess I'm growing
flowers but sometimes I get really angry
and fly off the handle commit herbicide
I don't mean to I say I didn't mean it
baby you'll be all right then I cry and
wear a diaper for 2 days a flower is
nothing more than an educated weed
and like all weeds all living things
need to be extinguished like a life
support machine or or a cigarette which
I won't be able to smoke anymore if the
fascists in the state government have
anything to say about it with that damn
proposition 421 tobacco is a plant
people and and and if it comes out of
the ground we should be able to smoke it
like coal and opium next caller yeah I
got a question why is everybody on the
radio named Maurice God I pray to the
great Gardener in the sky that you've
been fixed I hope they sniffed your nuts
off because spreading your seed could be
a disaster do you do you have a question
a question God so many vegetables on
this show tards yeah that guy was
talking about bugs and plants that eat
them I got a better solution put
pesticide in the sprinklers my kids love
it I mean the ones that lived oh lovely
you're a lovely human being you [ __ ]
imbecile you morons in this town are
spreading like weeds like little bastard
dandelions I wish I could just pop every
one of your goddamn heads off hello
lineate you're on gardening with Maurice
yeah I heard what you said about bonsai
trees and you know what you can stick
that green thumb right up your
ass yes another man who grows miniature
plants so he can feel like a giant a
real man loves enormous trees that he
can
have his way with chopping them down and
using the wood to Fashion rocking horses
and and suggestive whirly gigs okay
we're running out of time literally but
again like a seed sewn in a hurricane or
a mushroom spore from outer space the
garden goes on I'm Maurice until next
time dig a hole and plant
yourself that was the show that
generates more phone calls than any
other on wct gardening with Maurice if
only the world was less like this I
could use a smoke hey put that out and
more like this I could use a smoke you
murderer I might have children one day
smoking kills unless you kill first if
you're around a smoker you will die
smokers may look relaxed and like
they're having fun don't believe it vote
Yes on proposition 421 let's Outlaw
smoking everywhere even in people's
homes and allow honest C to legally kill
anyone who smokes let's live in a world
without smokers prohibition Works let's
prove it let's move up the food chain
it's time to smoke The Smokers vote Yes
on proposition
421 want to be too scared to go outside
the news is next Leanne for wct State
controlled news proed up breaking news
is skateboarding making your son
impotent and how to find out today's top
stories why hatred is good for you
foreigners worse than we thought and our
top story concerns the death of recently
cleared police officer Frank ten peny
his body was found in the aftermath of
the recent Riot set off by his aquid
coroners took several days to identify
the body which had been mutilated and
Stripped by the homeless more on the
riot of the century how do we keep it
from happening again Richard is on the
streets with rescue
workers Leanne I don't know if you've
ever covered a riot
but the scene here is
amazing rescue workers are opening up a
car with the jaws of life right here it
is so cool I'm on fire hey shut up [ __ ]
I'm interviewing I'm what you're ruining
my report shut up hey hey rescue guy
come here come here Richard burs wct
news how's it going you dumbass I'm
trying to save this woman get out of
here I'm trying to save this woman that
bag yeah we'll see if I give you any
beers from my news truck you overpaid
prick Leanne this town is going to need
some healing back to
you hey why don't you use the jaws of
life on your fat wife
dude did you hear me rank him that was R
I'm so glad you're okay Richard hey baby
are we off the air I looted some great
stuff for our apartment a fat bare skin
rug a new blender a double Ender
currently we have no more information
and in entertainment news The Comeback
of the Year disgraced drunkard mad dog
who was recently saved from jumping to
his death by a mystery assistant is on
top of the charts with a new album and a
sellout tour planned yes people the
waight is over mad dog is back on the
top where I belong baby number one now I
want to set the record straight at this
point I've been hearing all kinds of
[ __ ] like I was drunk and I was on some
drugs and I had a breakdown or some [ __ ]
I was never in a hotel and lost
venturist that's [ __ ] they just
hating on a player man they didn't
hating on me since I was in baby shoes I
was in the studio yeah took a little
time off I watch y'all rappers get out
there and try to do your thing but now
I'm ready to drop this dog [ __ ] on your
wacky ass rappers I got a new manager
his name is Carl Johnson and we going to
take this rap game to a new level by
storm for the second time yeah [ __ ]
sign up right now to get in my whole
roster it's going to be big yeah get
take a number ho take a number I'm
Leanne for wctr news this is the end and
a new beginning